(Man:)It's a shame about those
scientists ripping you off.
(Man:)I expected a higher
ethical standard
(Man:)from our friends in Sweden.
(Leonard:)It's actually pretty common
in our field.
(Leonard:)Not much you can do about it.
(Man:)Well, for the right
amount of money,
(Man:)if you know where they live,
(Man:)there's, uh, plenty
we could do about it.
(Sheldon:)Did you hear
that, Leonard?
(Sheldon:)There's plenty we
could do about it.
(Sheldon:)Do you have a card?
(Penny:)Okay, here we go.
(Penny:)Now everyone can see.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(clears throat)
(Penny:)Where do we stand
on cross-eyed Mike?
(Raj:)You know he won't be
looking at other girls.
(Howard:)Unless they're sitting
on the end of his nose.
(Penny:)Okay, okay, okay.
Thumbs down.
(Howard:)Next.
(Bernadette:)Ew, check out
his tiny teeth.
(Bernadette:)He looks like
a man-dolphin.
Wait, if he's good in bed,
she can throw him a fish.
(high-pitched):
I love you, Amy.
(squeaking)